Craig Seymour Collection, 1968-2006 SC 144
Archives of African American Music and Culture
- 5. Audiovisual (excluding interviews)
  - 5.2. Commercial media, Nearly 1,000 CDs of commercially released audio is included in this collection. The CDs are a mixture of published and unpublished releases. The unpublished releases are primarily promotional copies sent out in advance of an album release for review. The unpublished record
    - Scenario [Single] // Tribe Called Quest (Musical group), 1992; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3697
      ZD45496
    - Rush [Single] // Kleshay, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3698
      JERV
      KLE2CDX
    - We Got a Love Thang [Single] // Peniston, CeCe, 1991; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3699
      AMCD 846; 390 486-2
    - Just Friends (Sunny) [Single] // Soulchild, Musiq, 1977-, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3700
      Def Soul
      572 812-2
    - I Care (Soul II Soul) [Single] // Soul II Soul (Musical group), 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3701
      VSCDT 1560
    - Get Into You [Single] // Deep Bros., 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3702
      Coalition
      ART 007CD
    - One Sweet Day [Single] // Carey, Mariah; Boyz II Men (Musical group), 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3703
      660603 5
    - The Foundation [Single] // Xzibit (Musician), 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3704
      RCA 64708-2 07863
    - Thinking of You [Single] // Sister Sledge (Musical group), 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3705
      8122-77007-2 A4515CD
    - Fun [Single] // Da Mob, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3706
      INCredible
      INCRL2CD
    - Fallin' 4 Another [Single] // Mungal, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3707
      72435 5123 29
    - Masquerade [Single] // Gerideau, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3708
      Inferno
      CD FERN 7
    - Give Me You/Sexy [Single] // Blige, Mary J., 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3709
      MCSXD 40230/155 727-2
    - Waiting [Single] // D'Influence, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3710
      7559-64377-2 A4378CD
    - Holdon [Single] // En Vogue (Musical group), 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3711
      7559-63796-2 E3796CD
    - Shorty (Got Her eyes on Me) [Single] // Jones, Donell, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3712
      Laface/Untouchable
      74321 74890 2
    - The Real Thing [Single] // N.Y.G. (Musician), 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3713
      YZ883CD2 4509-99195-2
    - What's Going On [Single] // All Star Tribute, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3714
    - Whitney Dancin' Special [EP] // Houston, Whitney, 1988; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3715
      A28D-1
    - Heaven [Single] // Mary Mary (Musical group), 2005; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3716
    - Keep on Keepin' On [Single] // MC Lyte, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3717
      Electra/East West
      7859-63951-2
    - Girls It Ain't Easy [Single] // 4 Corners (Musical group), 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3718
      CDP1224
    - Love the One You're With [EP] // Vandross, Luther, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3719
      Epic/LV
      6610612
    - Where Do We Go From Here [Single] // Williams, Vanessa, 1963-, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3720
      314 578 102-2
    - Boy Next Door [Single] // Jamelia, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3721
      7243 8 89431 0 9
    - For The Cool in You [Single] // Babyface (Musician), 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3722
      659494 2
    - Emotion [Single] // Destiny's Child (Musical group), 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3723
      672111 2
    - Turn it Up [Single] // Raja-neé, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3724
      31458 8369 2
    - On the Down Low [Single] // McKnight, Brian, 1969-, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3725
      CDP 1498
    - Take Me Higher [EP] // Ross, Diana, 1944-, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3726
      7243 8 82386 2 5
    - Seven Days [Single] // Blige, Mary J., 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3727
      MCSTD 48083
    - Lose My Breath [Single] // Destiny's Child (Musical group), 2004; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3728
      675491 2
    - Earth Song [Single] // Jackson, Michael, 1958-, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3729
      662695 5
    - Magic [Single] // D'Influence, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3730
      Echo
      ECSCD45
    - My Flame [Single] // Williams, Vanessa, 1963-, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3733
      MECP 461
    - More to Love [Single] // Case (Musical group), 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3734
      0447-3325*1A2
    - For Real [Single] // Tricky, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3735
      ISCD 1027-2
    - Ain't No Mountain High Enough [Single] // Brown, Jocelyn, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3736
      Dance Pool
      DAN 666359 2 LC 6772
    - Thank God It's Friday [Single] // Kelly, R., 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3737
      CD 395
    - Gold [Single] // Knight, Beverley, vocalist, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3738
      7243 5098306
    - Against All Odds [Single] // Carey, Mariah, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3739
      669887 5
    - Word Love [Single] // Rhianna, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3740
      Sony Soho Square
      673011 5
    - Sweetheart [Single] // Dupri, Jermaine, 1972-; Carey, Mariah, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3741
      01-666413-14
    - We Need a Resolution [Single] // Aaliyah, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3742
      7243 8 97771 0 9
    - Boy You Knock Me Out [Single] // Ali, Tatyana, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3743
      MJJ Music/Epic
      666937 5
    - The Places You Find Love [Single] // Jones, Quincy, 1933-, 1989; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3744
      PRO-CD-4458
    - Saturday [Single] // East 57th ST, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3745
      AM:PM
      AM:PM 582 375 2
    - Soulflower [EP] // En Vogue (Musical group), 2004; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3746
      Funky Girl/ Beat Exchange
      6617
    - Buddy X 99' [Single] // Dreem Teem 'V' Neneh Cherry, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3747
      4 Liberty
      LIBT CD 33
    - "4 Shure" [Single] // Groove Theory (Musical group), 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3748
      018 2127 1500
    - How Many Licks [Single] // Lil' Kim, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3749
    - Curiosity [Single] // Hall, Aaron, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3750
      MCAD-11228
    - Crazy Love [Single] // McKnight, Brian, 1969-, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3751
      CDP 1454
    - Slow Jams [EP] // Jones, Quincy, 1933-, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3752
      POR-CD-8255-R
    - Love for Free [Single] // Rell (Musician), 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3753
      Roc-A-Fella/Def Jam
      DEF 221-2
    - Luv 4-2 [Single] // Watford, Michael, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3754
      PRCD 5275
    - Iz U Wit Me [Single] // DA Youngsta's, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3755
      PRCD 5169
    - Horse & Carriage [Single] // Cam'Ron, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3756
      Untertainment/Epic
      ESK 41224
    - Caught in the Middle [Single] // Roberts, Juliet, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3757
      PRO-CD-7031
    - Night Nurse [Single] // Sly & Robbie, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3758
      Inoks
      PRCD 7317-2
    - Bring Back Your Love [Single] // Christión, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3759
      DEF 172-2
    - Get Crunk/Lovers & Friends [Single] // Lil Jon & The East Side Boyz, 2005; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3760
      TV-2698-2P
    - Let Me Love You [Single] // Hathaway, Lalah, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3761
      DPRO 14128
    - How Many Ways [Single] // Braxton, Toni, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3762
      Laface
      LFPCD-4081
    - Young Girl Bluez [Single] // Biz Markie, 1964-, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3763
      Cold Chillin'/Warner Bros.
      PRO-CD-6415
    - Separate Ways/Family Affair [Single] // Hathaway, Lalah, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3764
      DPRO 14246
    - Keep it G.A.N.G.S.T.A. [Single] // Nate Dogg, 1969-, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3765
      PRCD-1726-2
    - Beep Me 911 [Single] // Elliott, Missy, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3766
      PRCD 9998-2
    - U Don't Know Me (Like U Used To) [Single] // Brandy, 1979-, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3769
      PRCD 8978
    - Free [Single] // MYA, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3770
      Ruffnation/Warner Bros.
      PRO-CDR-100366
    - Homies and Thuggs [Single] // Scarface, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3771
      Rap-a-Lot
      7087 6 12797 2 6 DPRO12797
    - Could You Be Loved [Single] // Cole, Debbe, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3772
      Next Plateau/ London
      CDP 1078
    - One in a Million [Single] // Aaliyah, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3773
      PRCD 8012
    - I Don't Wanna Be Alone [Single] // Shai, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3774
      Gasoline Alley
      GASSP-3761
    - Mama Said [Single] // Anderson, Carleen, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3775
      DPRO-14248
    - Passin' Me By [Single] // The Pharcyde, 1992; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3776
      PRCD 4987
    - Up and Down [Single] // Lawrence, Billy, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3777
      PRCD 9908-2
    - Street talkin' [Single] // Slick Rick, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3778
      DEF-328-2
    - Don't Front [Single] // MissJones, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3779
      Step Sun
      TBCD 133-2
    - Please Don't Go [Single] // Immature (Musical group), 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3780
      MCA5P-3746
    - Timeless [Single] // Big Bub, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3781
      U5P-1167
    - Jeeps, Lex Coups, Bimaz & Benz [Single] // Lost Boyz (Musical group), 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3782
      Uptown
      UPT5P-3442
    - Riddle [Single] // En Vogue (Musical group), 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3783
      PRCD 7448-2
    - I'm Cool [Single] // Hustlechild, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3784
      PRCD-1791-2
    - Taking Everything [Single] // Levert, Gerald, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3785
      PRCD-7371-2
    - Satch Blows the Blues // Armstrong, Louis, 1901-1971, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3830
      ACK 86578
    - Milestones // Davis, Miles, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3831
      ACK 85203
    - Miles Davis at Newport 1958 // Davis, Miles, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3832
      ACK 85202
    - Miles Davis 'Round About Midnight // Davis, Miles, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3833
      ACK 85201
    - Miles Davis Jazz at the Plaza // Davis, Miles, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3834
      ACK 85245
    - The Best of Miles Davis and John Coltrane (1955-1961) // Davis, Miles; Coltrane, John, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3835
      ACK 61090
    - Fo' Sho'/ Never Give Up [Single] // Adams, Yolanda, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3836
      PRCD 1716-2
    - Pocketbook [Single] // NdegéOcello, Me'Shell, 1969-, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3837
    - God Cares // Marrow, Esther, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3838
      EMI Gospel
      7243 8 20368 2 1
    - Make Me Better // Nesby, Ann, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3839
      It's time Child
      RTI 00200
    - Metro Area // Metro Area (Musical group), 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3840
      Hydroelectric
      ENVCD002
    - Get Crunked Up [Single] // Iconz (Musical group), 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3841
      Slip-n-Slide
      PRCD 7468-2
    - Pony [Single] // Ginuwine, 1975-, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3842
      550 Music/ Epic
      36K 78373
    - B-Sides [Single] // Destiny's Child (Musical group), 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3843
      CSK 42717
    - Love is All We Need [Single] // Blige, Mary J., 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3844
      MCA5P-3984
    - The Heat is On [EP] // Isley Brothers, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3845
      85315
    - Surrender // Killings, Debra, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3846
      Verity
      82876-53481-2
    - King of Rock [Deluxe Edition] // Run DMC, 2005; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3847
      Legacy/Arista/ Profile
      69558
    - Strip Tease // Lady Saw, 2004; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3848
      VP Music
      VPCD1683-2
    - Tougher Than Leather [Deluxe Edition] // Run DMC, 2005; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3849
      Legacy/Arista
      69559
    - Do Thangz [Single] // Men of Vizion (Musical group), 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3850
      550 Music/ Sony
      36K 78422
    - Lady May [Ep] // May West, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3851
    - Converstions With the Queen [EP] // Queen Pen, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3852
      Uptown/ Universal
      158736
    - Jene Reign [EP] // Jene, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3853
      19312
    - (I'm) Hurting Inside // Ralph, Sheryl Lee; Marley, Cedella; Marley, Sharon, 1989; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3854
      CD 17711
    - Things we Do For Love [Single] // Brown, Horace, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3855
      374631445-2
    - Black Hand Side (Al's Remix) [Single] // Latifah, Queen, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3856
      374631196-2
    - Body Bumpin' [Single] // Public Announcement (Musical group), 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3857
      AMSAD 00640
    - The Place Where You Belong [Single] // Shai, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3858
      MCA5P-3124
    - Say I [Digital Mourice Radio Edit] [Single] // Milian, Christina, 1981-, 2006; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3859
      Island/ Def Jam
      ISLR 13202-2
    - Can't Nobody [Single] // 1 Life 2 Live, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3860
      LaFace
      LEPCD-4382
    - Lay Your Troubles Down [Single] // Winbush, Angela, 1990; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3861
      CDP 248
    - The Nu Nation Project [Single] // Franklin, Kirk, 1970-, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3862
      GospoCentric
      INT5P-6649
    - 5 Song Sampler [EP] // Brown, Raphael, 199-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3863
    - Get Retarted [Single] // Can-I-bus, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3864
      53216
    - Do That Dance [EP] // Rodgers, Nile, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3865
      Video
      VACM-1027
    - Take it to the Head [Single] // Brand Nubian, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3866
      ASCD-3585
    - Never in My Life [Single] // Cherrelle, 1991; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3867
      Tabu
      28965 1703 2
    - She's All I Got [Single] // Cozier, Jimmy, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3868
      J Records
      J1DJ-21070-2
    - Emotional [Single] // Thomas, Carl, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3869
      BBPCD-9355
    - Yesterday [Single] // Morgan, Debelah, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3870
      374633086-2
    - Just Keep Thinking About Me [Single] // Gaynor, Gloria, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3871
      LGDJ-81359-2
    - Kiss Kiss Kiss [Single] // Ono, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3872
      Mind Train
    - Steelo [Single] // 702 (Musical group), 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3873
      Biv Ten
      314530738-1/2/4
    - Strong Enough [Single] // Holloway, Loleatta, 1992; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3874
      PRCD 8625
    - Bulls Eye [EP] // Talent, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3875
      Rockland/Interscope
    - I Adore You [Single] // Wheeler, Caron, 1992; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3876
      Prospective
      31458 8016 2
    - Through the Tears [Single] // Morgan, Meli'sa, 1992; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3877
      Pendulum
      PRCD 8600-2
    - The Best of Gladys Knight and The Pips [Sony Expanded] // Gladys Knight and the Pips, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3884
      CK 85965
    - There's No Living Without You [Single] // Downing, Will, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3885
      CDP 960
    - Sampler [EP] // Bow Wow (Musician), 2005; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3886
      Sony Urban
    - Can't Play Around [Single] // Brown, Kathy, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3887
      Cutting Records
      CD 278
    - What I Need [Single] // Waters, Crystal, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3888
      CDP 1409
    - Hands Up (So So Def Remix) [Single] // TLC (Musical group), 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3889
      82876-51180-2
    - Luke's Sheila [Single] // Campbell, Luther, 1960-, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3890
      Luke Records
      PRCD 7672-2
    - I Want You [Single] // Jackson, Janet, 1966-, 2004; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3891
      CD-ROM mini disc
    - My Dreams [EP] // Michele, Yvette, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3892
      Loud Records
    - Renee [Single] // Lost Boyz (Musical group), 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3893
      422-854 584-2
    - Again [Single] // Jackson, Janet, 1966-, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3894
      7243 8 92229 2 0
    - Play At Your Own Risk: Featuring Lil' Jon Remix [Single] // Planet Patrol (Musical group);Lil' Jon, 199-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3895
      tbcd 319
    - Black Hand Side (Radio Version) [Single] // Latifah, Queen, 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3909
      374631174-2
    - One Night at Shelter NYC // Regisford, Timmy, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3910
      Dance Wicked
      DWCDA001
    - Lucky Strike // Morel (Musical group), 2004; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3911
      YoshiToshi
      YRCDLP10
    - The coffession Booth Sampler // St. Juste, 2004; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3912
      Sony Urban Music/Columbia
      CSK 56485
    - Bad Ass Kid [Single] // Pendleton, Malik, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3913
      PRCD 8933
    - Life on Earth // Vega, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3914
      Capitol
      COP 7243 5 20161 2 9-V
    - In Person an evening With the Supremes // Supremes (Musical group), 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3915
      021 159 416-2
    - Van Hunt // Hunt, Van, 1977-, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3916
      DPRO 7087 6 17931 2 7
    - The Black Widow [Advanced copy] // Strings, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3917
      Sweat Records
      AEK 69892 S3
    - Funky Stuff: The Funk Essential Sampler, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3918
      SACD 684
    - The Original // Sarai, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3919
      Epic/Sweat
    - Pru // Renfro, Pru, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3920
      7243 5 23120 2 3-S
    - Black Love: Music for Your Soul, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3921
      MCA5P-4136
    - Arista Records Spring 2001 Sampler, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3922
      ARCD-4714
    - Chapter 1: Love, Pain and Forgiveness // Johnson, Syleena, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3923
      JADV-41700-2
    - Love & Life [Mix CD sampler hosted by Funk Master Flex] // Blige, Mary J., 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3924
    - Love Story [Single] // Before Dark (Musical group), 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3925
      RADV 67691-2
    - Want That Old Thing Back/ Running Your Mouth [Single] // Notorious B.I.G. (Musician), 2005; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3926
      PRCD 302082
    - Closer // Plastikman, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3927
      Novamute
      3081-2 724596308 127
    - This Time // Savage, Chantay, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3928
      RDAV 67607-2
    - The Trouble With Being Myself // Gray, Macy, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3929
    - Underground // Monk, Thelonious, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3930
      K 63535-S1
    - Solo Monk // Monk, Thelonious, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3931
      K 63533-S1
    - Criss-Cross // Monk, Thelonious, 2003; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3932
      K 63537-S1
    - Tracie // Spencer, Tracie, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3933
      CDP 7243 8 34587 2 4-V
    - The Immortal Soul of Al Green // Green, Al, 2004; 4 Audio Discs
      CD 3934
      4 CD box set
      Hi/ The Right Stuff
    - The Pwer of the String // Jackson, Paul, Jr., 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3935
      7243 5 21477 2 4V
    - Let's Get it: Thug Motivation 101; Album Sampler // Young Jeezy, 2005; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3936
      DEFF 16308-2
    - Reality Check [Exclusive Bonus CD] // Juvenile (Musician), 2006; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3937
      Alantic
    - Street Life/ Mad Brothas Know His Name [Single] // Intelligent Hoodlum (Musical group), 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3938
      Tuff Break
      31458 8246 2
    - Like it was Yesterday [Single] // Brandy, 1979-, 2004; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3939
      STCD 301506
    - Tuck Me In [Single] // Scott, Kimberly, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3940
      DIDP 094468
    - I thought I Meant the World to You/ I Pray [Single] // Warren, Alysha, 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3941
      Polydor
      POL 940
    - Victory/ Bad Boy's Been Around The World remix [Single] // Diddy, 1969-; Family, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3942
      78612-79155-2
    - That Kind of Man/ Honey Lookin' Laced [Single] // Babyface (Musician), 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3943
      34K 78443
    - Back in Town [Ep] // Dax Riders, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3944
      Subsc
      MCAR-25645-2
    - Say it Again [Single] // Nneka, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3945
      422-854-648-2
    - Maverick A Strike [EP] // Quaye, Finley, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3946
      550 Music
      68506
    - Gitty Up [Single] // Salt-n-Pepa (Musical group), 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3947
      314-570 100-2
    - Never Make a Promise [Single] // Hill, Dru, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3948
      Island Black Music
      314-572 082-2 JK02
    - Tell Me it's Real [Single] // K-Ci & JoJo, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3949
      MCADS-55551
    - Men in Black [Single] // Smith, Will, 1968-, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3950
      COL 664724 1
    - I Can Love You/Love is All We Need [Single] // Blige, Mary J., 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3951
      MCADS-55362
    - Hypnotize/ I Got A Story To Tell [Single] // Notorious B.I.G. (Musician), 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3952
      78612-79092-2
    - It's Me Again [Sampler] // Tweet, 1971-, 2004; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3953
      STCD 301576
    - Boyz N da Hood [Sampler] // Boyz N da Hood (Musical group), 2005; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3954
    - Keepin' it Real [EP] // Knight, Beverly; Simmonds, Stephen; Charlotte, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3955
    - Dueces Wild [Sampler] // King, B. B., 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3956
      MCASP-4094
    - Stranger On Earth [Sampler] // Lina, 2000; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3957
      PRCD300165-2
    - I Dare You [Single] // Black Rob (Rapper), 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3958
      01-666483-17
    - If You Really Wanna Know [Single] // Dorsey, Marc, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3959
      01241-41564-2
    - Say…If You Feel Alright [Single] // Waters, Crystal, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3960
      MECP 182
    - Black Butterfly [Single] // Sounds of Blackness (Musical group), 1994; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3961
      PSSAD 0018 2
    - Automatic Lover (Call For Love) [Single] // Real McCoy (Musical group), 1995; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3962
      07822-12877-2
    - 1999 [Single] // Sanchez, Roger, 1967-, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3963
      Pride
      PM1005-2
    - Southern Hummingbird [Sampler] // Tweet, 1971-, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3964
      PRCD 1720-2
    - Afterschock [DJ Mix] // DJ Aphrodite, 2002; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3965
      V2 Music
      V2ADV-27129-2
    - Respect to DJ Deep [DJ mix] // DJ Deep, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3966
      Astralwerks
      ASW 69969
    - Ahead of the Competition 3.7 [DJ Mix] // DJ Envy; Big Mike, 199-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3967
      ING
    - R&B8: Warm-Weather Jumpoff [DJ Mix] // Dj Envy; Big Mike; Tapemasters INC., 199-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3968
    - R&B 10: Warm-Weather Jumpoff pt. 3 [DJ mix] // DJ Envy, 199-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3969
    - R&B part 5 [DJ Mix] // DJ Envy, 199-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3970
      Miskeen
    - R&B 14 [DJ Mix] // DJ Envy, 199-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3971
    - Latin Lover [Single] // Mills, Stephanie, 1957-, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3972
      Maw
      MAW-043
    - Cruisin [DJ Mix] // DJ Envy, 199-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3973
      Varcity
    - Bach Logic [DJ Mix] // DJ Whoo Kid, 199-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3974
      Shadyvill.Biz
    - Rap the Vote: A project of Rock the Vote [DJ Mix] // DJ Whoo Kid; Jadakiss, 199-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3975
    - R&B 2004 [DJ Mix] // Streetsweepers, 199-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3976
    - The Regulator [DJ Mix] // Streetsweepers, 199-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3977
    - Streetsweepers disc2/S [DJ Mix] // Streetsweepers, 199-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3978
    - Welcome to da Backwudz // DJ Smallz and Da Backwudz, 2005; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3979
      SSM
    - The Whyte Out: Southern Smoke Collector's Edition [DJ Mix] // DJ Smallz & Chyna Whyte, 2005; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3980
      Fear Factor
    - Dirty R&B Winter Edition: Cold as Ice [DJ Mix] // Tapemasters INC; DJ Smallz, 2005; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3981
    - Mary J. Blige Entourage [DJ Mix] // KeyZ; Big Mike, 200-?; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 3982